http://www.cemnet.com/content/policy/privacy.aspx

Conferences
13 January 2021, Cemtech Live Webinar: Cement Plant Emissions Monitoring and Control Solutions
8-11 February 2021, Cemtech Middle East & Africa Virtual Event
Policy
Tradeship Publications Ltd recognises the importance of privacy, security and data protection to our customers and partners.
Our approach to privacy at Tradeship Publications Ltd is our commitment to transparency in our privacy program. We aim to achieve this by providing clear and understandable notices of our privacy practices that enable our customers and partners to make meaningful choices about how we collect, use and disclose personal information about them.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide you with transparency of our operations, and it is designed to help you understand how we use and safeguard the personal information we hold about you, including information that may be collected from your online activity with us. This Privacy Policy also informs you about your rights in relation to our processing of your personal information.
Where we get your personal information
Through our websites, our mobile apps, or any other tool or delivery platform through which we make our content available
When you interact with us through social media websites and other websites and apps;
As a result of your subscribing to or contracting for our services;
As a result of your attendance at our conferences, webinars and other events, or at events not organised by us where you interact with our staff;
When you communicate with our staff, including, for example, through email;
Through our own research, through our partnerships and from third parties that provide it to us (e.g. Your personal details are listed as an event attendee for a third party industry event we are covering).
Types of personal information processed by us
Personal and business contact information, such as name, address, telephone number and email address;
Business contact data such as your employer’s name, your employer’s address, your role, your business telephone number and your business email address;
Financial information, such as your credit/debit card number or other billing information;
Information necessary for providing services to you, such as user IDs and passwords, product and service preferences and contact preferences;
Geo-location data such as your IP address or physical location;
Details of the services you have purchased from us or which you have enquired about, together with any additional information necessary to deliver those services and to respond to your enquiries;
Any additional information relating to you that you provide to us
Information you provide to us through our customer surveys.
Grounds on which we process your personal information
We will only process your personal information in a fair, lawful and transparent manner.
The processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation; or
The processing is necessary in connection with any contract that you have entered into with us, or to take steps prior to entering into a contract with us; or
We have a legitimate interest in carrying out the processing for the purpose of fulfilling our regulatory and compliance obligations; or
We have a legitimate interest in carrying out the processing for the purpose of contacting you, subject always to compliance with applicable law; or
We have obtained your prior consent to the Processing (this legal basis is only used in relation to Processing that is entirely voluntary – it is not used for Processing that is necessary or obligatory in any way).We may combine personal information you give to us and other information we collect about you. When combined, this will be treated as personal information and we will only use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
How we protect your personal information
We employ physical, electronic and managerial control procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorised access to your information.
Who we share your Personal Information with
Service providers and partners. We retain service providers and partners to manage or support certain aspects of our business operations on our behalf. These service providers may be located in the EEA, US or in other locations and may provide services such as service delivery, report personalisation, advertising and marketing activities, IT services, email service providers, data hosting, and management or support of our websites. We may also share your personal information with accountants, auditors, lawyers and other outside professional advisers, subject to binding contractual obligations of confidentiality. We also take steps to provide adequate protection for any transfers of your personal information in accordance with applicable law.
Affiliates. We may for our legitimate interests share your information with other companies under common ownership or control with us who will process your information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy and subject to appropriate safeguards. These companies may be based within or outside of the EEA and, in some cases, in countries which do not afford the same level of personal information protection as may be found, for instance, in EU countries. All such companies are, nevertheless, bound by an intra-group agreement under which they are required to maintain strict organisational and technical measures to protect your personal information.
Compliance with law and protection of people and property. We may share your information when we believe in good faith that such sharing is reasonably necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities or to comply with legal process. We may also share your information in situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Privacy Policy, or to respond to the claims of violation of the rights of third parties and/or to protect the rights, property and safety of Tradeship Publications Ltd, our employees, users, or the public. This may involve the sharing of your information with law enforcement, government agencies, courts, and/or other organisations.
Business Transactions. As we develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses, or sell some or all of our assets. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets or the assets disclosed in connection with the due diligence for any such transaction.
Your rights
To exercise any of the rights below, please email or write to the Data Protection Officer at the address at the foot of this page:
Right to object
You have the right to object to the processing of your personal information where we have exercised the right to process on the grounds of our legitimate interest.
Marketing emails you receive from us include an unsubscribe instruction (usually found at the bottom of the email) that you may use to stop receiving future marketing-related emails.
Right to withdraw your consent
Where you have given us your consent to process your personal information and we use this as the only basis to process your personal information, you may withdraw your consent at any time.
For example, you may withdraw your consent from marketing emails by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe link usually found at the bottom of the email. Please note that we may be unable to provide you with the full benefit of our Sites, or services, if you choose to withdraw your consent.
Correction of errors in information
You can ask us to correct any errors in your personal information that we hold and process. If you are unable to update your personal information through our online services, please make a request by email or write to the Data Protection Officer at the address shown on the foot of the webpage.
Right to erasure
If you request us to do so and there is no valid reason for us to retain it, we will erase your personal information without undue delay.
Right to restriction
You are entitled to seek the restriction of processing if there is a disagreement between us as to whether the right of erasure applies. You may seek this right:
For the time needed to verify whether information is accurate if you have contested its accuracy; or
Where you feel that we no longer need the data but you do for the purposes of a legal claim; or
You have objected to the processing but we seek to establish that we have compelling legitimate grounds for overriding your objection.
Where this right applies we will temporarily remove the data from our systems so as to avoid further processing and we will flag the restricted data in a way that makes it clear that processing is restricted.
Right to object to profiling
You may object to our processing of your personal information where we:
predict your service preferences, for example, by monitoring your browsing behaviour when you visit or website or apps; or
rely on automated decisions that have legal consequences or significantly affect you.
Right to data portability
Where we process your personal information by automated means and the processing is either based on your consent or a contract with you, you can request that we transfer your personal information in a commonly used machine-readable form to a third-party system.
We are not responsible if the processing systems are incompatible such that your personal information cannot be read by the third-party system.
Right to make a complaint
Our headquarters are in Dorking, UK. If you live in the EU, you have the right to raise a complaint with the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) or with the Supervisory Authority in the EU country in which you feel that your rights were infringed.
ICO contact details may be found at this link: https://ico.org.uk/
If you live outside of the EU, privacy laws in your country may also you give this right.
Access to your Personal Information
You have the right to access your personal information that we maintain about you and is held by us in paper records or electronic systems. You can make a request by email or write to the Data Protection Officer at the address shown on the foot of this page.
How long will you keep my data?
We will only retain your personal information for as long as is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which it is collected. This may vary according to the nature of your relationship with us.
We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, regulatory or operational requirements. To see when this Privacy Policy was last updated, please see the “Last Updated” section below. In this Privacy Policy “we”, “us” or, “our” means Tradeship Publications Ltd and “you” refers to you the individual.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please address them by email to privacy@CemNet.com or by writing to The Data Protection Officer, Tradeship Publications Ltd, Old Kings Head Court, 15 High Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1AR, UK.
Last Updated: This Privacy Policy was last updated on 15 May 2018. This Privacy Policy is published by Tradeship Publications Ltd, Registered in England and Wales under Company Registration No 02218297 with its registered office at Old Kings Head Court, 15 High Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1AR, UK.
regregSubscription
Subscribe to International Cement Review
12 issues of the leading cement industry magazine, your choice of complimentary handbook, plus unlimited access to CemNet.com News, Articles and HD Videos.
£ 205 / US$ 315 / EUR 260
CemNet.com Sitemap
About
Contact
Cement News
International
Trading
Freight Markets
13 January 2021, Cemtech Live Webinar: Cement Plant Emissions Monitoring and Control Solutions
8-11 February 2021, Cemtech Middle East & Africa Virtual Event
Tradeship Publications Ltd © 2020 | No part of this website may be reproduced without prior written consent from the publisher.
